Jordan Alexis

alexisjordan842@gmail.com ● alexisjordan842@yahoo.com ● (646) 625-8972 ● Brooklyn, NY 11236

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer | Computer Programmer | Web Designer | Office Clerk | Data Analyst

Executing the Day → Planning the Future → Impacting Results →

Watching the Bottom Line → Solving Issues → Supporting Teams → Serving Clients → Cleaning

Data

- I have experience using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Cloud Computing, and others to help build websites for clients or myself.
- Experience using Adobe Creative Cloud applications such as Premiere, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and XD to help make my websites and other jobs I must do.
- Experience entering client information into a database and checking that the data is secured and correct. Dealing with customers who need help with orders placed and account information.

Skills		Specializations	
Office Management	Calendar Management	Relationship Development	Training Development
Client Relations	Project Management	Adobe XD, Dreamweaver,	Benefit Administration
Form Processing	Research	Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat,	MS Office, Word, Excel,
Social Media-	Data-driven Analysis	Premiere.	Outlook, PowerPoint
Manager	Accts Payable/Receivable	Hootsuite	HTML/CSS, PHP,
Office Planning	Data Analytics	Visual Studios Code	Responsive Design,
		Eclipse	jQuery
		GitHub	

Professional Experience

Unadat – Manhattan, NY Software Engineer Intern July 2021 - Aug 2021

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the Executive Director of Unadat. Managed a cross-functional team to develop a dark mode for the Unadat portal site. Supported operations through data-driven analysis and people metric reporting. Collaborated with the design team in devising and user-testing the color scheme and functionality.

- Optimized dark theme for the mobile and progressive web app.
- Debugged independent research to overcome roadblocks and obstacles.

WBAI Radio 99.5FM NYC – Brooklyn, NY Spring Intern

Jan 2019 – May 2019

SNAPSHOT: Reported to Director of Development. Provided support with keeping up with the shows and events through social media posts and the Event Calendar. Provided customer service to the listeners, helped with the support of the "BAI Buddies" (membership that the supporters of the station were called), mail-in prizes that they won, and merchandise they brought from the website or on-call.

- Organized the photos and the text that the event calendar and social media had.
- Handled social media from February to May

The Challenge Publisher Group – Brooklyn, NY Multimedia Internship

July 2018 - Aug 2018

SNAPSHOT: Reported to Organizer of the Group. Managed the project to get the newspaper "The New American" into the modern age using Adobe InDesign. She distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York using email and placing the papers in mailboxes.

Creating a timeline to show where the project would be by the end of the internship.

Brooklyn Neighborhood Improvement Association (BNIA) – Brooklyn, NY Aug 2017 – Aug 2017 Office Assistant | Intern

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the director of BNIA. Provided support for the Summer Youth Interns by connecting them to their site providers. Helped with entering the work hours that the interns had on their timesheets and ensuring that the interns were not casing any disruptive actions that would impede the workflow of the site.

St. John's Recreation Center – Brooklyn, NY Multimedia Developer Internship.

July 2017 – Aug 2017

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the site provider. Learned how Adobe products operated and assisted other students with any issues using the adobe system. Hands-on experience with a radio room and learning the basics of audio and video production.

Charles Churn Christian Academy – Brooklyn, NY Day Care Worker

July 2014 to Aug 2014

SNAPSHOT: Reported to the Site Manager. Assisted in creating and providing activities for the kids. Helped carry 5-20 pounds of equipment/bags to the trips they went on—support of keeping them out of harm's way.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Multimedia Computing and Information Science - Brooklyn College, Brooklyn, NY, Aug 2019 - Present

Associate degree, Multimedia Programming, and Design - Borough of Manhattan Community College, Manhattan, NY, Aug 2017 – May 2019

Credits Towards Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications: Associate degree - Technical Career Institute, Manhattan, NY, Jan 2017 – May 2017

Credits Towards Computer Information Systems (Game Design Concertation): Associate degree Bramson Ort College, Queens NY, Oct 2014 – Jan 2017